Ah, am I audible? Hello everyone.
Good evening to all.
Hello. Hello.
Thank you for your answers for the uh
for subscribing. Welcome back.
[laughter]
Thank you for the three months. Thank
you.
Hello. Hello. Hello. Tima Vinsa.
Welcome. Welcome. Hello for your
answers. Welcome.
Hello.
Uh give me a minute. Okay.
95.
So today we will be playing uh Valerant.
I haven't touched this game for
an year I think.
I mean last year was last year but yeah
I think I touched it a little bit during
Joathon stream.
Um but yeah, this today's stream will be
the 42nd [music]
uh [laughter]
series of me playing Valerant.
I heard there's like new gun and stuff
which came out and like new agents which
came out and wiper has lower now
[laughter]
they're having lower in battle right now
crazy
uh so many things
it is really interesting too so yeah
today we will be
diving into that so sure we are going to
be diving into Malorand.
One second. Let me make it so that um
Give me a minute. Give me a minute. Uh
huh.
Announcement did not get made. God.
Yeah. Just like yesterday, this stream
as well, there'll be some technical
issues here and there. Don't mind it.
Please don't.
I'm still uh revamping my setup a little
bit.
a little. So yeah,
the job stream
I was watching I show speed earlier the
Ethiopia thingy for today. Yeah,
[laughter] I actually wanted to stream
in the morning, but I was so tired, man.
Yesterday, I think I slept at 6:00 a.m.
or something because no, I after
yesterday's stream, [music]
I happened to like I I was like, "Okay,
I need to fix these stuff. There were
like seven crashes which happened uh
back in the back end when I started my
stream. Now, I have to I fixed all of
that. I talked [music] a bit to Chad GPT
about how to fix some stuff and I got
some crazy ideas for the 24x7 channel.
Uh how I could add like a ving viewer
ving system for Twitch YouTube kick. Uh
so you can vote what type of content you
want for the always on channel. Hey I
was like uh gathering ideas and writing
them down. Then I slept. I woke up late
too.
But yeah.
Okay. Let me switch to the game.
Uh,
one second. I think I need rac.
Okay. What the?
Give me a minute. I had my keybinds of
valerin on my mouse. So, I can't.
So, yeah.
Uh,
okay. We are ready.
Are we ready? Okay. Um, it's all the
screen.
Give me a minute.
Uh,
why does the create patch does not work?
O, create the message, man.
Okay.
Come on.
Okay. announcement will be made that I'm
live automatically any moment now
we we
patch do the second Yeah. Come on. Come
on.
What?
[laughter] I hate this thing. Why does
it break? Every single time I want to
stream, it doesn't do it. No.
tomato.
No, bro. No, no, no, no, no, no, bro.
No,
no, no, no, no, fam. No.
What the heck? Didn't they fix this
yesterday? Okay. Ah, okay. A game.
Dang it. I'm sorry. I didn't test this
stuff.
[gasps]
Okay. Valerand,
do you see the game?
Okay. Uh
Nothing. One second.
11 150. What is happening?
11 150. What is 150?
Stop crashing. Let me stream 11 150 to
90.
Huh?
>> One second.
>> I'm still live, right? At least tell me
I'm live.
>> [laughter]
>> I'll cry.
So many technical issues.
Uh
stop crashing. Okay. Close this.
I don't need to.
Uh okay. Uh YouTube. Uh is it working?
YouTube. Okay. YouTube is working. Good.
Good. Good. Wait, wait, wait. I'm going
switch here and
close this. Okay. And uh
uh give me a minute.
Wait, did bread just res? Wait, wait,
wait. What?
Hold up.
Wait. Let me open my chat. Oh, wait.
Oh my god.
Wait, what?
Uh,
am I seeing things? Okay, I'm seeing
things. Sorry. Uh,
okay. Hi, uh, Valerent.
I'm sorry for the technical issues. They
changed the whole UI and everything.
Crazy.
They changed all the UI and stuff. Am I
online? I'm supposed to be offline. What
the heck? Wait, wait, wait. What? I'm
supposed to be offline.
Starters type offline. Yeah, now I'm
offline. Yeah, don't mind it. I'm
offline. Yeah, no one can see me that
I'm playing the game. [gasps] What is
this? Random. All one side. What is
this?
So many
stuff now.
Uh
viewing.
Although what is this? Join the
conflict. Choose a side. Choose.
What?
What did this just Why did it just open
up the
join the conflict? What is this?
Bandit friends.
Access your FTW with your
What is FTW platform?
What is FTW?
Huh?
For the win. For the win is a rare
challenge run allowing you to compete in
multiple types of challenge across your
nation or region region. Unleash your
creativity and push your skills to the
limit in game. Our rewards and races
crazy
challenge starts on
starts from January 7. Oh, okay. Oh,
this is nice.
Oh,
am I lagging?
I am. All right. Am I lagging? Am I
lagging right now?
It's a bit scared that I am lagging.
Okay. What the
What the
I hate making you guys wait too much
like this. I'm really sorry again.
Uh,
Bro, it's not even working.
I hate this.
H.
I have an idea. I'll just do this.
Next stream I do. I have to make sure
none of these issues happen.
Yeah, I have to make sure none of these
issues happen again
really much. So,
okay.
Hello, Stream Hub World. Welcome.
Thank you for joining in.
Method five not allowed. What the heck?
Oh.
Uh, my bad. I have to do this.
Uh, okay. Wait. Uh.
Uh, which is which? Why do I have so
much junk? Uh,
the
what the
one second.
Okay. Save.
I I should have tested it tested
multiple times and then done the stream.
Wow.
I'm making guys f comment.
Okay, announcement is made.
Oh my god,
finally. Okay, I'll fix it later, I
guess. Um,
this is just dumb. Uh,
uh, one second.
Copy this.
I had to like fix the structure. No, I
that's why uh all of this stuff have had
to happen.
This can't even I need to fix that.
[snorts] Anyway, let's just peacefully
just play the game. Uh I don't need to
do that. Uh close the browser. My PC is
lagging.
Uh
why do I have a high ping?
What? Wait, wait, wait. M.
Hold up.
Hold up. Wait a minute. Why do I have
hyping?
Uh, that is bad. Oh no.
Wait. Who is he eating up?
Oh my god. Who is
uh close this?
Wait, why do I have hyping?
Ah, man. I'll just play, man.
I don't care.
Uh,
any matching
Akayashi?
Is it supposed to look like Okay, now
it's working.
>> Okay,
let me know if I'm lagging or not. I'll
fix it. Okay.
Wait, what's with the black screen?
What's with the black screen?
Uh
uh.
What's happening?
Wait, why is it black screen though?
Huh? Didn't I just get into a game?
What is happening?
Where am I? Um, Gecko.
>> Death match. Warm up.
>> I haven't played this game in a while,
so I don't know how things are.
Is my sensitivity this low? What the
heck?
191. Why is it so low? I still three.
Okay.
Why the
Who is that guy?
Ah, nice try.
>> Dominating.
Oh my god, this is hard to get used to.
It's been a while.
fight.
Ah,
I heard you.
Ah
yeah.
Ah,
What the?
[groaning]
>> Wow, nice shots.
What? Keep that lit.
[laughter]
Oh, this is the new gun. Oh, this is the
new guy.
Oh, [laughter]
that's a new gun.
>> [laughter]
>> I'm dying a lot.
Wow.
How do I even defeat you with a gun like
this?
W shots.
>> [laughter]
>> How is [\h__\h]
doneing?
Oh my god, I'm playing so badly.
>> Oh my god.
10 kills remaining.
Come on. Come on.
[groaning]
Come on.
My Oh my god, that scared me. Oh, wait.
My god.
>> Ah, that was such a bad idea.
Oh my god. Scary, scary, scary.
Oh my
One kill remaining.
>> What else?
Nice.
It was a bit ling money. What is who?
What is this
on random free lorders? Way more
ultimates first five to win
all round among
competitive spike rush.
Let me try this.
Match found.
Prepare
to defend. Oh, it's a random event.
I forget how to play characters.
Someone's there.
>> Get out of my way.
>> One enemy remaining.
>> Initiated.
Why? I can't just do this.
>> Wow.
Oh, it's every time it's diff different.
Oh, okay. Okay. Okay. I kind of
understand uh how it works. So every
stage you get like uh uh every stage you
get like uh team eliminated. What? Hello
Solar.
Hey, they added this thing here.
I think they're coming back. Honestly,
>> get out of my way.
>> Ah, I couldn't. How about you? I'm doing
great.
>> OPEN UP THE SKY. YOUR FEAR.
>> That's three. Not ready yet. READY.
>> One enemy remaining.
>> Wow.
Why is he Why is this guy not reloading?
>> What you doing from
>> Wait, you have unlimited
that you you can like what?
Oh, wait. Is this a new agent?
Never seen that guy before.
Uh,
hey, they added this thing here.
interesting.
>> Anyway, just wanted to drop by and say
hi. Yeah, take care. Thank you for
dropping by. It really means a lot.
>> That
should run.
Too slow.
>> Spike planted.
>> One enemy remaining.
My ultimate ready.
>> Wow, this is nice.
>> My ultimate
>> last round in the
Um
why is my mouse buttons not working or
something?
Ah it's in arators that's why Valerant
>> going out.
Ah, that was so dumb.
>> That was so dumb.
>> Last player standing.
>> Ah, the reload. Poor.
>> Welcome to my world.
Switching sides.
>> There's two outlaws here.
Interesting.
Oh, you can't drop the spike apparently.
Shadows traveling.
>> Take flight. Cover going out.
>> Ultimate ready.
>> Ah, that was so dumb.
One enemy remaining.
>> Ultimate ready.
>> Let's turn the
>> damn. Wait, did that guy water guy
ultimate change or something?
animation.
>> My isn't ready.
Uh
oh, I'm this uh new character or
something. I don't even know what this
does.
My ultimate is ready. Enemy spott.
Enemy spott.
>> Oh my god.
MY
>> 30 seconds left.
>> There
cold.
Last player standing.
>> Ah, I couldn't.
I couldn't. I couldn't. I couldn't.
Oh, what is this character?
What does this do?
I don't know.
Uh, stealth special guided salvo.
Uh,
locating target.
>> Nice, nice, nice, nice.
Oh sh What's happening? What's
happening? What's happening? What's
happening?
>> Last player standing.
>> Ah.
by one match point,
>> brah.
My is ready.
>> I am the hunter.
>> Ultimate ready to grave
decoy.
>> [laughter]
>> Ah, why me?
>> Last player standing.
Not another step.
>> Defenders win.
>> Why?
Yeah, that that game mode was fine. I
want to play more of that.
Match found.
Let me drink some water.
Uh, I think our creators has an update
today,
like a 1GB update, I heard.
Not sure though.
Reloading.
>> This game mode does make you want to use
all these agents ability, you know,
rather than choosing what agent you want
to play.
I realized that
Steam, stop making my game lag.
>> What? How? How did it re
uh
>> Oh, is this like a new gun?
Where did my stream die?
Did my stream die? What the heck? Wait,
why? Twitch is die.
Wait, what?
Did my What the
go?
>> Enemy mid.
Enemy
spotted. A
>> You want to play? Let's play.
>> One enemy remaining. My ultimate's
ready.
>> 30 seconds left.
What are they doing
>> to play? Let's play.
>> Last player standing. 10 seconds left.
>> Ah,
the stupid lag and the crashes pop up.
Oh my god.
Wait, what was the crash though?
Stream announcer or
event.
>> Reloading.
>> Uh,
what is going on?
Snare tripped.
You are powerless.
>> Can't use that.
>> You should run.
>> Last player standing.
It's me.
>> Oh sh so dumb.
>> It's you and me.
>> Last round before the switch.
Hello stupid daddy. Welcome.
Are you able to watch my stream? I don't
think my stream is lagging, isn't it?
Uh
are you able to I can watch? Wait, is it
not lagging on Twitch?
Uh weird.
My
>> run.
[sighs]
Ah.
>> Last player standing.
>> Fear spikes. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay.
>> ADAPT OR DIE. I'm playing well after
like after like one year or something. I
haven't played well at all.
>> I think No, no, I think I did play last
year. Only once or twice.
>> What is this? This is nice.
>> A lot of things happened here. No, so
many new guns.
characters
>> mystic bloom. Ah,
do you play this game?
Do you play this game?
I don't I I don't know why. [laughter]
I feel feel a bit I don't know if it's
rude to say this.
>> I feel bored playing this. It's just
shooting. Is it because I've been
playing extraction shooter?
>> Is that the Is that the reason why?
One enemy remaining.
>> Oh, that's fair.
>> Face your fear.
>> 30 seconds left
>> because you're playing solo. Really?
You should tri my fine. Ah,
>> a quick reboot. I'll be fine.
>> Oh, this is a new gun. It's a It's a
heart shaped gun.
Nice.
And this new bandit gun is nice.
Really nice.
The the It's like a heart. The
ghost now which has a heart. I think
it's the new one or something
like a red heart kind of thing.
>> When did they change this area?
Reload.
>> Ah, that's down.
>> Oh, nice.
>> Heal up. Heal up. Heal up. Nice. TO RUN.
>> AH, nice shot.
>> Defenders win. [laughter]
[sighs]
>> GG. [laughter]
That's the first time I seen a GG like
Indian GG. J I J I
Oh, I'm MVP. Oh, I played bad.
Uh, how do you get Asians again? I don't
have this character. There's this
recruit
for 8,000.
>> I should s the end of the game.
Crazy.
Do they still have the Kingdom Hearts
thingy?
I think they do, right?
Oh, the new character passed away. Oh,
here. There you are.
New Kingdom points. Oh, it's not Kingdom
Hearts. Kingdom points. Yeah.
8K. Did they change it? Wasn't the cap
was 6K, right? Did they change it to 8K?
>> Stop showing me the B. Uh, wait.
>> Game crashed.
begin.
>> Counter measure. [groaning]
Spike planted.
>> My stuff is crashing hard. Backend
stuff. Sammy is crashing.
Uh, I want to change the gun.
>> Joke's over. You're dead.
Reloading.
>> They're not They're not ready.
>> One enemy remaining.
>> You did good.
>> Joke's over.
Oh my god, guys.
>> Your duty is not over.
>> Oh my god.
>> How do I get ultimate?
Oh, it's this guy.
>> Stopping fire.
over there.
>> You want to fight it?
>> One enemy remaining.
>> No distractions.
Open up the sky.
>> Ah, you
kid.
>> 30 seconds left.
>> Oh, nice.
Last round in the half.
Enemy spotted.
>> Enemy down. My ultimate IS READY.
YOUR DUTY IS NOT OVER.
>> One enemy remaining.
>> Nice.
>> Switching sides.
>> Okay.
>> Bad luck. I miss seeing this character.
I'm out of here.
>> Oh, wait. You can't [laughter] dumb
down.
>> Thank you for the hydrate.
es
barrier deployed.
>> Can't use that.
>> Ultimate ready.
Hold them to their grave.
>> Got one. Multiple enemies.
>> 30 seconds left.
>> Can't use that.
>> You want to play?
>> Last player standing.
10 seconds left.
>> A nice try. Okay, I'm doing so much.
Oh, clove.
I don't know how to play. Oh my gosh.
Not sure though.
>> Right here.
I can't use that.
>> Not ready yet.
>> Have one of these.
>> The hunt begins.
One enemy remaining.
>> Oh my god. Nice.
>> Why is this guy saying easy when he's
losing?
>> What does this character do?
Uh ech target surface. Uh I don't
understand
>> lover.
OFF YOUR FEET.
TOO MUCH EGOISTIC. There are there was
>> last player standing.
When did I make it like this?
>> Off your feet.
>> Why are they snitching?
>> I'll find you.
>> Why are they being rats?
Oh, nice shots.
>> Not in a good way.
>> Should I place some stars in this
reality?
What character am I?
My
>> ready
>> shot.
>> Wait, what? How do I exit?
>> You will NOT KILL MY ALLY. YOU'RE DEAD.
>> Last player standing. 30 seconds left.
>> Useless individual.
>> You will not kill my ally.
>> Lock
death.
>> Astra. Nah.
Yeah, this character is a bit
complicated indeed.
suppressing.
>> Suppressed.
>> What is happening?
Enemy spotted.
>> Last player standing.
>> I know exactly.
>> Toaster. My ready.
>> Okay. Oh my eyes.
Hello dragoner. Welcome.
Yeah. KO. It's been a while
again.
New skins there.
Oh, they have their style. Ah, this
literally is my new mortal raid thingy.
Uh, so cool.
I don't want to spend money, man. I I
I'm done with that life.
Premiere.
>> I'm all right. What about you? I'm also
doing great.
It's been a while, so I thought of
uh playing this game. Apparently, I had
it installed, so I had to do the update.
Also, I want to rant for a bit. Okay.
Why is the Riot Games new launcher so
bad?
How do I uninstall the game? How do I
change the proper uh install location
and stuff?
I can't find the settings of the
launcher.
What? Oh, they Why did they remove the
settings?
Hello, Nan Rajbird. Welcome. Hello.
Hello. I'm doing well. How are you?
It's been a while. I've seen you play.
Yeah,
I've been playing Arc for a while now.
Oh, stupid jock. It was closed.
>> I didn't know it. No.
>> Nah. No. I don't know that.
>> Holy lord. How did I hit that shot?
Ultimate is ready. Initiate.
>> Last player standing.
>> Ah,
take your Okay. Launcher is trash. Uh,
raw game. [laughter]
Riot game. Yeah.
And the [\h__\h] I I love the UI change and
stuff. It's similar to the Chinese
launcher. It's good. But
>> still though, you got to give us the
settings now.
>> OFF YOUR FEET.
LAST PLAYER STANDING.
>> H.
OH,
I like that you changed that much. Oh,
yeah. They changed the UI a lot.
They changed the UI a lot.
Yeah. How does the map rotation work in
this game?
What? Where? Who?
>> Huh?
Open up the sky.
>> Ah,
>> I finally be back. Hi. Take care.
>> One enemy.
>> A so close here too.
>> I'm the thing of I didn't get neon.
Oh, there
>> somebody's there
IS READY.
AH, the shield though.
>> Oh,
[laughter]
>> weapon. One enemy remaining.
>> Oh, nice.
>> Collateral.
>> I can feel it. It feels like I'm really
sorry for those who are watching my PC.
Even Valerant is hard to play.
Placing
swarm grenade.
>> Good. My ultimate is ready.
>> Grenade out.
There
>> on cool down.
>> Go, GO, GO.
>> JOKE'S OVER. YOU'RE DEAD.
>> One enemy remaining.
>> Nice.
>> I don't know how to play that character.
That said,
>> John's
ready.
>> Enemy spotter.
>> A
>> I have the highest
paying of the century now.
I'm supposed to get like 30 or
something.
What happened?
Oh, this is not a character.
>> [screaming]
>> That's a good
>> blind with fear.
>> I couldn't.
>> What the heck? [clears throat]
Attackers win.
>> They still need to give Hello Alec.
Welcome.
Good evening.
They still need a giveaway to mute chat
in game chat.
I interface.
Where is Manila
curious? Wait, I want to check where is
the Manila server
from
what the
what is this spelling again? M A N
I L.
Oh, it's Philippines. Oh. Oh, they have
a server now.
Oh, do no.
Who is this person?
What was that person?
Oh, the wiper.
A white bird.
Okay, we'll play a few more games. Okay.
Oh, they have a splash screen like this.
That is nice.
What is this? Unranked.
I don't want to play a competitive. as
well play this.
Did the event even get made? No. What
the heck?
The moment I change the structure stuff,
everything is like
different.
Why didn't it get made weird?
main thumb doesn't exist. What the heck?
Yeah, after shrimp. Now I got to do some
debugging.
My back end is all messed up.
>> No, you don't. My
>> one of these
got here.
>> Last player standing.
>> COME ON, LET'S GO.
>> ONE enemy remaining. Nice
>> planted.
>> Going up.
>> My ultimate ready. Oh.
He just
he just fell
wanted to sacrifice for the boys or
something.
I'm running out of water and need some
hot water.
multiple enemies.
Enemy
destroyed.
>> What am I doing?
>> Foolish.
>> My ultimate is ready.
>> Enemy spotted. B.
One enemy remaining.
>> You're welcome.
>> Not another step.
>> 30 seconds left.
>> Nice.
>> Local interfered.
What is this? Uh, wait, wait, wait.
What? Who am I playing? Harbor has this
thing. Uh,
I love the transition thing. See, see,
see. Kind of cool though.
on the loose.
>> One enemy remaining.
>> Last round.
>> Oh, now I'm a different agent.
Nice.
>> My ultimate is ready.
>> Oh,
>> my ready. Enemy
kill.
>> Enemy spott.
>> I got to wait.
>> Last player standing. One enemy
remaining.
>> You out me.
That was a That was a good I was happy
with that.
They are SO DEAD.
>> GET OUT OF my way.
Last player standing.
>> Ah,
ONE BY ONE.
I'm too far. I'm too far. I'm too far.
>> I'm too far.
Can I only use the
>> thingy once or something?
One enemy remaining.
>> Joke's over. You're
>> 30 seconds left.
>> Ah, no.
marked one.
>> Ah, that's right.
here.
>> Okay.
area.
>> You want to play?
>> One enemy remaining.
>> Decoy
is ready.
Oh, nice.
>> I am the hunter.
>> Yeah.
Oh, yeah. Blue protocol. New season is
coming, right?
Uh I won't be here at home though.
H
Oh, it's 18th this coming. Okay. I think
I think I I will have time to play it.
Yeah. Yeah. After examin.
Hi. Uh
how long did we play today?
I'll have to wrap up and go to bed.
I would have to wrap up and go to bed
soon.
So then, okay, we can wrap it up. Plus,
my internet is a bit odd today.
It's going down and up.
Yeah, it was fun. I'll wrap it up over
here. No.
Hope you all had a good one
watching me play my Lord.
Even if it's uh for a little bit, I had
a good time today.
So yeah, thank you for tuning in to my
short stream.
After my exams are done by on Sunday,
Monday onwards, I'll try to my best to
uh do longer streams. Okay.
Plus, we had some technical issues
behind the scenes to in the back end.
Um I have to sit down and fix all of
that, too. [laughter] It's such a
headache.
But yeah, I enjoyed it today. Thank you
all for giving me your time of the day
to watch me and support me. Really means
a lot. Thank you for talking with me as
talking with me as well. Anyhow, I'll
see you guys tomorrow. Tomorrow is what
is there, right? Yeah. Hey, I'll see you
guys tomorrow.
Probably I'll play Fortnite. Not sure.
Depends. Maybe arc. Who knows?
Hi. With that said, I will wait. But
that's it. I will wrap it up here.
Okay, let me redirect you.
Let me redirect you to my V channel.
Okay. Hi. Have a good one everyone.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
Bye-bye.